（忆往昔）
我名叫吉米·诺瓦克
My name is Jimmy Novak.
上帝选择我做更重要的事情
God has chosen me for a higher purpose.
你再不能和你的家人在一起
You can never be with your family.
卡西迪奥 你保证我家人平安无事
Castiel, promise my family will be okay,
我就照做
and I'll do it.
- 爸爸 - 我不是你爸爸
- Daddy? - I am not your father.
卡西迪奥 你已经夺走了我的一切
Castiel, you took everything from me.
- 这姑娘是谁 - 克莱尔·诺瓦克
- Who is this girl? - Claire Novak.
克莱尔有问题 她需要一位父亲
Claire's troubled. She needs a father.
- 她有问题 - 是我造成的
- She's got issues. - Because of me.
我先失去了第一个父亲…
First, I lose my first dad…
又失去了第二个
And then I lose my second.
是谁杀了他们 毁了我的生活呢
Who killed them and trashed my life?
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean winchester.
我们可以解决他
We'll take care of him.
这样他就不会再来烦你了
so he won't bother you anymore.
不要
No!
- 你妈妈在哪 - 她去「寻找自我」了
- Where's your mother? - She went to go "find herself."
你答应过的 小卡
You promised, Cass!
我有帮助你的义务
I have a responsibility to help you.
我还是得一个人走
I still gotta go it alone,
但我也许可以偶尔打打电话
but I could maybe call sometimes.
不要
NO!
迪恩有麻烦了 他情况并没有好转
Dean's in trouble. He's not getting better.
我妈说那个血印只不过是个诅咒
Mother says the mark is just a curse.
是可以去掉的
It can be removed.
如果有治愈办法 我们就去做
If there's a cure, we'll do it.
有什么后果之后再应付
and deal with the consequences later.
我不能失去你
I can't lose you.
（如今）
艾米莉娅
Amelia?
Amelia?!
吉米
Jimmy?
是你吗
Is it…you?
卡西迪奥走了 是我
Castiel is gone. It's me.
对不起 真对不起 我…
Sorry. I'm so sorry. I never…
我到处找你
I looked everywhere for you.
我以为我又失去了你
I thought I lost you again.
没事
It's okay.
没事了
It's okay. It's…
It's okay.
我回家了
I'm home now.
怎么回事
What's happening?
我们女儿怎么样了
How's our girl?
克莱尔怎么样了
How's Claire?
不要
No!
不要又这样
No! Not again! No!
不要
No! No!
你很安全 艾米莉娅
You're safe, Amelia.
你回家了
You're home.
艾米莉娅
Amelia?
Amelia?!
吉米
Jimmy?
是你吗
Is it…you?
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
我真不该离开
I'm so sorry I left.
我到处找你
I looked everywhere for you.
[邪恶力量 第10季第20集]
（奥克拉荷马州 塔尔萨）
你跑到这种地方来做什么
The hell you think you're doing in here?
明天是我生日
Come on, it's my birthday tomorrow.
你多大了 12岁吗
How old you gonna be? 12?
50了
More like 50.
我找一个叫罗尼·卡特莱特的人
I'm looking for a guy named Ronnie Cartwright.
他是这里的常客
He's supposed to be a regular around here.
罗尼·卡特莱特
Ronnie Cartwright?
不管你卖什么 我不买 丫头
Whatever you're selling, I ain't buyin', sweetheart.
我需要你的帮助 罗尼
I need your help, Ronnie.
我在找一个人
I'm trying to track somebody down.
从没见过
I ain't never seen her before in my life.
她叫艾米莉娅
Her name's Amelia.
她已经失踪多年了
She's been missing for a few years,
但她日记上写着
but according to her diary,
她约好跟你见面的
she was supposed to meet up with you.
我没见过她
I ain't never met her.
你本打算介绍她认识一个神棍
You were gonna introduce her to some miracle worker.
我不知道你在说什么
Look, I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
我不认识这女人
I don't know that lady.
我更不认识什么神棍
And I for damn sure don't know some miracle worker.
否则我还会落到这种田地吗
If I did, you think I'd be in a dump like this?
滚开吧
Now piss off.
回你的女童军吧
Go back to your girl scout troop.
- 她是我母亲 - 我管你
- She's my mother. - I don't care.
你能再看一眼吗 或许…
Can you just take another look? I mean, maybe…
我说了 我没见过她
I told you, I ain't never seen her before.
你最好也别再烦我了
Now I better never see you again.
我叫你离我远点了
I told you to stay the hell away from me.
你是最后见过我妈妈的人
You were the last person to speak to my mom.
我得找到她
I need to find her.
我不认识艾米莉娅·诺瓦克 懂吗
I don't know Amelia Novak. You got it?
我没说过她姓什么
I never told you her last name.
等等
Wait!
拜托
Come on.
911 有什么紧急情况
9-1-1, what is your emergency?
我在小巷里发现一个晕倒的女孩
Um, yeah, found some girl passed out in the alley,
就在大陆街苏茜酒吧旁边
uh, uh, by Susie's bar on Overland.
我们马上派救护车过去 先生
We'll send an ambulance right away, sir.
能告诉我她是否还有呼吸吗
Can you tell me if she's still breathing?
（塔尔萨纪念医院）
- 谢谢赶来 - 嗯 应该的
- Thanks for coming. - Yeah, of course.
小卡 我们当然乐意帮忙
Cass, look, we're always glad to help,
但我和克莱尔关系可不怎么好
but Claire and I aren't exactly on the best of terms.
我来好吗
I mean, should I even be here?
我需要你们两个人的帮助
I need help from both of you.
你们也都曾是问题少年 你们理解她
You were both troubled teens. You speak her language.
好吧 她怎么样了
All right. How is she?
我还没进去呢 我在等后援
Well, I-I haven't gone in yet. I was waiting for backup.
后援
B-backup?
三个汉子一个妹子 进去吧
Three men and a lady. Let's do this.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
你带他来干什么
And why the hell did you bring him?
好极了
Awesome.
警方在你的紧急联系人名单上
Um, the… the police found my number.
找到了我的号码
in your emergency contact list.
嗯 那是个错误
Yeah, well… that was a mistake.
你可以走了
You can go now.
克莱尔
Claire…
你为什么会去酒吧
Why were you at a bar?
我没有
I wasn't.
克莱尔 你怎么会在一间酒吧外的小巷里
Claire, what were you doing in an alley outside of a bar?
错误的时间去了错误的地点 这辈子都这样
Wrong place, wrong time. Story of my life.
你不跟我们说清楚到底怎么回事
Look, we're not leaving until you tell us.
我们不会走的
what the hell really happened.
如果你希望我们走
So if you want us gone…
就说实话
talk.
我在找我妈妈
I was looking for my mom.
我想找到我妈妈 告诉她她毁了我的人生
I wanna find my mom and tell her she ruined my life.
- 你妈妈没有… - 她抛下了我
- Your mom didn't… - She left me,
我爸也是
and so did my dad.
但吉米死了 是吧
But Jimmy's gone, right?
在天堂逍遥呢
Has it easy up in heaven.
所以我只能去数落我妈了
So…mom's the only one left I can tell off.
最后有人见到你妈妈是什么时候
When's the last anybody heard from your mom?
我跟奶奶住一起时
When I was living with my grandmother,
她会给我寄明信片
she used to send me postcards.
这是最后一张
This is the last one.
我奶奶死前不久收到的
I got it just before my grandma died.
两年前了
Two years ago.
再就没了她的消息
Nobody's heard from her since.
（柯蒂斯汽车旅馆）
是从当地一家汽车旅馆寄出的
It was sent from a motel here in town.
我就住在那里
That's where I've been crashing.
我在苏茜酒吧找一个叫罗尼·卡特莱特的人
I was at Susie's bar looking for a loser named Ronnie Cartwright.
妈妈的日记里写着约了见他
Mom's diary said she was gonna meet him.
之后不久便失踪了
around the time she disappeared.
他打昏我之前
Before he knocked me down,
说出了她的名字
he remembered her name.
他知道什么的
He knows something.
艾米莉娅找他做什么
Why was Amelia looking for him?
她想找神迹
She went looking for miracles.
她想找你
She went looking for you.
这都怪我
This is all my fault.
小卡 就算是吧 你又能做什么
You know, Cass, say it is. What can you do about it?
找到艾米莉娅
Find Amelia.
她是找天使的路上失踪的
She did disappear trying to hunt down an angel.
- 或许是我们的案子 - 这无法确定
- Might be a case. - Yeah, but we don't know that.
差不多了 拜托 给我找个出气筒吧
Close enough. Come on, give me something to punch already.
开玩笑的 我挺好
I'm kidding. I'm fine.
我好着呢
I'm just…I'm fine.
我们回酒吧
Why don't we go back to the bar,
看能不能找到这个罗尼
see if we can track down this Ronnie guy, huh?
嗯 先跟克莱尔说一声我们去哪
Yeah. We should let Claire know where we're going first.
好嘞
Perfect.
- 该死 - 这可好
- Damn it. - Well…
她要么又去找罗尼了
She either went looking for Ronnie again or, uh…
要么回旅馆拿东西 准备再次跑路了
Yeah, or she went to go grab her stuff before taking off again.
她有脑震荡 或许走不快
Well, she's got a concussion. Maybe that'll slow her down.
好了
All right.
我去汽车旅馆 你们去酒吧
I'll head to the motel. Y'all check out the bar.
小卡 你这样帮克莱尔
Hey, Cass, listen, what you're doing for Claire.
找她妈妈
and helping her find her mom…
这是件好事
It's good. It's a good thing.
但是呢
But?
但怎样算到头呢
Well, where does it end?
我不是犯浑 但事实就是
I'm not trying to be a dick, but truth is,
你并不是她爸爸
you're not her dad.
事实上 你对她而言什么都不是
In fact, you're not anything to her.
只能一直提醒她一个已经逝去的人
expect a-a constant reminder of someone that's gone.
不 我…
No, I'm…
要为她遭遇的一切负责
Responsible for everything that's happened to her.
我只是想说
Look, I'm just saying,
她已经自力更生很久了
she's been surviving on her own for quite a while now,
她能做到这一点
and… and then partly because.
部分原因就是她不用对谁负责
she doesn't have anybody to answer to.
没有…
You know, there's…
没有谁拖累她
there's nobody holding her back.
她刚刚进了医院
We just found her in a hospital.
你难道想说她自己过会更好吗
You telling me that she'd be better off on her own?
我想说她自己过会更坚强
I'm saying she might be stronger on her own.
着什么急啊
Yeah! What's the rush, huh?
赶去打别的少女吗
Heading out to beat down another teenager?
那小贱人先动手的
That bitch attacked me!
说什么呢 伙计
Poor choice of words, pal.
艾米莉娅·诺瓦克
Now…Amelia Novak.
她在哪
Where is she?
- 不说吗 - 什么
- No? - What?
- 迪恩 - 听着 罗尼 怎么样
- Dean. - Listen, Ronnie, what do you say, huh?
我们可以玩一整天 除非你告诉我
We could do this all day, unless you wanna tell me.
你知道关于艾米莉娅的一切
everything you know about Amelia.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
我见过艾米莉娅
I met Amelia.
但她是最后一个 我发誓
But she was the last one, I swear.
最后一个什么
Last one of what?
我为一个信仰治疗师工作
I worked for a faith healer.
不 他是真有本事
No, he was the real deal.
我之前是个瞎子
Hey, I was blind.
他治好了我
He healed me.
说名字 快点
Give us a name. Now!
- 彼得·霍洛韦 - 好
- Peter Holloway. - Okay.
他治好我的眼睛后
Yeah, after he gave me my sight back, I…
他要我为他工作 当做报酬
Well, he made me work for him as…payment.
我招募候选人
I-I-I recruited candidates.
他有固定喜欢的类型
Yeah, he had… A specific type.
年轻…
Young but, uh…
迷茫
lost.
没人会找的人
Wouldn't be missed.
艾米莉娅也是「候选人」之一吗
Amelia was one of these "candidates"?
有些人他治疗
Some people, he healed.
也有些人…
But others, he, uh…
天呐
Oh, man.
我有一晚看到了他
Look, I saw him one night.
看上去 他好像在…
It looked like he was, uh…
我也说不清楚 他在…
I don't know… I don't know how to describe it, but he was…
他把一个人绑起来
He tied one of 'em up and…
他在…
He… he… he was, uh…
割伤他们
cutting on them.
那之后我就不干了 我离开了
Look, after that, I was done. Okay? I quit.
再也没有霍洛韦的消息了
I haven't heard from Holloway since.
可算回来了
Took you long enough.
你怎么…
How did you…
而且你登记用的名字是「克莱尔·诺瓦克」
Also, you checked in under the name "Claire Novak."
给你点专业性建议 用假名
A little pro-tip? Use an alias.
好吧
Okay.
克莱尔 我们只是想帮你
Claire, we just wanna help.
我没叫你们帮
I didn't ask for your help.
这弄得不错
You know, this is good.
挺厉害的
I was impressed.
你怎么收集到的信息…
How did you get the information that…
大都是落空的承诺和悔恨
It's mostly empty promises and regret, but…
但也留下了足够线索让我找到这儿来
there were enough bread crumbs to get me here.
你怎么拿到你妈妈的日记的
How did you get your mom's diary?
妈妈失踪之后
The motel manager sent mom's stuff.
旅馆经理把她的东西寄去了最后地址
to her last known address after she disappeared.
到处流转
It bounced around,
最终寄到了我一个寄养家庭到了我手上
eventually found its way to me at one of the foster homes.
你大老远跑来就为了数落她吗
You came all this way just to tell her off?
你跟你妈关系一直很好吗
You always get along with your mom?
根本没机会跟她相处
Never got the chance to find out.
我还是个婴儿时我妈就死了
My mom died when I was a baby.
很抱歉 我不知道…
I'm… I'm sorry. I didn't…
没事的 我后来有机会认识了她
Oh, no, it's okay. I-I got to know her later in life.
是的 我们处得挺好的
And, yeah, I suppose we got along okay.
什么
What?
干我们这行 死亡并不总是永别
In this line of work, death isn't always good-bye.
这不一样 我妈妈抛下了我
This is different. My mom left me.
「克莱尔 我就回家了
"Claire, I'll be home soon.
我们都会回家了「
We'll be home soon."
听上去不像是想抛弃你的样子
Doesn't sound like somebody who wanted to abandon you.
你查她信用卡记录了吗
Did you check her credit cards?
银行不肯把记录发给我
They wouldn't send me her records.
好吧 我知道你
Okay, I know you need to be.
想远离我们
somewhere far away from all of us,
但容我去拿电脑
but let me get my laptop.
教你怎么黑入她的信用卡记录
I'll teach you how to hack into her credit card records.
这能帮你查到相关线索
It'll help you get a lead on your mom.
教我 然后我就走
Show me, but then I'm gone.
听我说
Hey, listen,
我觉得这些打探消息的不是联调局
I don't think these guys snooping around are F.B.I.
- 我觉得他们是… - 猎人
- You know, I-I think they're… - They're hunters.
对不起
I-I'm sorry.
我就是想给你提个醒
I-I wanted to give you the heads up.
如果你闭好嘴
Wouldn't need a heads up.
也没这个必要了 罗尼
if you kept your mouth shut, Ronnie.
别这样
Hey, come on.
明白吗
Don't you see that?
别这样啊
Come on. No. W…
我的眼睛 别这样啊
My eyes! Come on, man!
我看不到了
I can't see!
好了
There we go.
不是吧 这么简单吗
Seriously? It's that easy?
是啊
Yes.
我还可以教你建立虚假信用卡账户
I can also show you how to set up fake credit cards.
这样在外面混能好过些
It will make life on the road a lot easier.
你们还做信用卡诈骗啊
You guys are credit card scammers, too?
是啊 猎魔又没工资
Yeah. Hunting monsters doesn't exactly pay the bills.
那你们为什么这么做
Then why do you do it?
帮助他人 改善世界
To help people, make a difference.
就这样吗
That's it?
这还不够吗
That's not enough?
你没事吧
Are you all right?
如果没人再这么问我 我就好了
Yeah, I will be when nobody ever asks me that again.
- 找到罗尼了吗 - 嗯
- You guys find Ronnie? - Yeah.
他交待了一个人 彼得·霍洛韦
Yeah, he gave up a name… Peter Holloway.
说是个信仰治疗师
Said he was a faith healer.
怎么 是天使吗
So…what? You thinking angel?
可能吧 听上去他是治好过一些人
Maybe, but it sounded like he has healed some people,
但却吸食其他人
but he may have fed off others.
好奇怪
Yeah, that's weird.
好吧 我查查这个彼得·霍洛韦
All right, let's look into this Peter Holloway guy.
克莱尔
Claire, um…
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
在热门店买的
I got it at the hot topical.
嗯
Right.
谢谢了吧
Um…thanks, I guess.
当地警方刚刚发出警讯
Just got an alert from local P.D.
罗尼的尸体刚刚在苏茜酒吧外被发现
Ronnie's body was just found outside of Susie's bar.
你们就是去找罗尼问话的
You were just supposed to talk to Ronnie.
你做了什么
What did you do to him?
我碰都没碰他
I didn't lay a hand on him.
迪恩 这话可不准确
Dean, that isn't exactly true.
我没杀他啊
I didn't kill the guy.
好吧 我穿上制服过去看看
All right, I'm gonna suited up and head back over there.
我也来
I'm coming with you.
I'm coming with you, too.
你也来吗
You wanna get in on this?
不了 我留下查霍洛韦吧
No, I-I should probably stay here and research Holloway.
好吧
Right.
小卡
Hey, Cass?
在酒吧发生什么了
What happened at the bar?
迪恩发火了 他情况越来越糟了
Dean snapped. He's getting worse.
警官
Officer?
克莱普顿和佩吉探员
Agents Clapton and Page.
小朋友呢
And your little friend?
嗯 今天是局里的「带女儿上班日」
Yeah. It's "bring your daughter to work" day at the bureau.
被害人是一起失踪案的嫌疑人
Uh, vic was a, uh, person of interest in a missing persons case.
什么情况
What do you got?
刺伤 穿透
Stab wound. Clean through.
不是抢劫
No sign of robbery.
钱包什么的还在身上
Wallet and everything was still on his person.
入口伤的红印是什么
What are the red marks there on the point of entry?
焦痕吧 不清楚
Burn marks, maybe. Don't know.
我们查了他的手机记录
We pulled his cell phone records.
袭击发生前给同一个号码打了两通电话
He made two calls to the same number prior to the attack.
打了一下 已经不通了
Tried the number, but the line's dead now.
大概是一次性电话
Probably a burner.
失陪了
Will you excuse me?
嗯
Yeah.
柯尔特恩警长
Sheriff Coltrane.
伤口看着像天使之刃
The wound looks like an angel blade,
但入口伤要更宽一些
but the point of entry is wider.
红印就不明白了
Can't explain those marks.
最棒的生日了
Best birthday ever.
好了 过来
Okay, all right, come here.
我查到彼得·霍洛韦的线索了
I, uh, got a lead on Peter Holloway.
很好 他大概就要逃了
Oh, good, 'cause he's probably about to split town.
罗尼死前打了几通电话
Ronnie made a few phone calls before he got shish kebabed.
你觉得他是给霍洛韦通风报信了吗
You think to give Holloway a heads up?
如果是 可能他就是因此被杀
If he did, that's probably what got him killed.
我们得赶在他逃跑前找到他
So…we gotta track him down before he bails.
好 根据郡记录
Great. Well, according to county records,
霍洛韦在离这儿三四十英里处有一座农舍
Holloway owns a farmhouse about 30 or 40 miles from here,
我交叉对比了
so I, uh, cross-referenced it.
艾米莉娅的信用卡账单
with Amelia's credit card receipts.
房子就在这里
The house is about right there,
而她在周围的餐馆和加油站
and she's been hitting up Biggersons and gas n' sips.
都待过
all around the area.
- 大概是在打探情况 - 是啊
- Probably staking the place out. - Exactly.
那我们还等什么 走吧
Well, what are we waiting for? Let's go.
克莱尔 你不能过去
Claire, you are not going out there.
她是我母亲
She's my mother.
那农舍可能是空的 也可能是陷阱
That house could be empty and it could be a trap.
太危险了
It's too dangerous.
我不能让你出事
I can't let anything happen to you.
出别的事吧
Anything else, you mean.
克莱尔 你不能去
Claire, you're not going.
- 你也不能去 迪恩 - 什么
- You're not either, Dean. - What?
刚刚在酒吧 跟罗尼
Back at the bar with Ronnie?
得了 小卡
Oh, come on, Cass.
他不肯交待 我就敦促了他一下
He wasn't gonna talk. I just… helped him talk.
迪恩 小卡说得对
Dean, Cass is right.
我们得控制血印
We need to keep the mark in check.
而且我们并不清楚会是什么情况
And we don't know what's out there.
或许你还是…
You know, maybe you should…
或许你还是留下吧
Maybe you should stay here.
你又要让我坐冷板凳吗
So you wanna bench me again?
好吧
All right. Fine.
我留下照顾孩子
I'll stay and babysit.
但如果发生什么情况
But if anything happens, anything at all…
嗯 我们会叫你的 别吵架
Yeah, we'll call you. No fighting.
嗯 跟她说去啊
Yeah, tell her that.
你俩都一样
Both of you.
能给我一瓶吗
Can I have one?
好像你等到合法年龄才喝酒似的
Like you never had a beer before you were 21.
好吧
All right. You know what?
如果我们一晚上都憋在这旅馆房间里
If we stay cooped up in this motel room all night long,
我会疯的
I'm gonna lose my mind.
告诉你 你已经疯了
Spoiler alert… you already have.
呵呵…来吧
That's… come on.
走吧
Let's go.
等这事结束
When this is over,
我…
should I…
我应该不再管克莱尔吗
should I leave Claire alone?
什么 不行啊 她是家人
What? No, man. She's family.
她不完全算家人
Well, I mean, she's not exactly family,
但也差不多了
but she's close enough.
你们有段过去的 就这样
I mean, you two have history. Simple as that.
那你并不觉得她自己生活会更好吗
So don't you think she's better off on her own?
小卡 她才刚满18
Cass, she just turned 18.
你18时就孤身一人去上大学了
You were alone when you left for college at that age,
不是吗
weren't you?
是 但那不一样
Yeah, but that's different.
怎么不一样 萨姆
How, Sam?
我只知道
Here's all I know…
独自生活 那不叫生活
Going it alone, that's no way to live.
如果她有你
You being there for her,
哪怕她自己认为她并不需要你
even if she thinks she doesn't want you to be there for her,
这对你俩也都有好处
that's good for both of you.
或许 最终吧
Maybe, in the end.
最终吧
In the end.
进洞
It's in the hole!
进洞喽
比尔·默里
Bill Murray?
《疯狂高尔夫》
"Caddyshack".
经典电影啊
It's a classic.
没看过 不感冒
Never seen it. Not a fan.
你好大胆
How dare you.
闹够了
You done?
嗯
Yeah, I'm done.
对你们这代人都无语了
I'm done with your whole generation.
你看到了吗
Did you… did you see that?
是进洞了吗 我没仔细看呢
Did that go in the hole? I wasn't watching.
- 球进洞了吗 - 《球场古惑仔》
- Did the ball go in the hole? - "Happy Gilmore."
算你狠
Well played.
- 谢谢 - 嗯
- Thank you. Mm. - Yep.
进洞了吗 进洞了吗
Did that go in? Did that go in?
看上去是废弃的
It looks abandoned.
是不是只有一个办法确定
Only one way to find out.
你们就干这个吗
This is what you guys do?
住在廉价汽车旅馆
Stay at cheap motels,
盗用信用卡
steal credit cards…
玩迷你高尔夫
Play mini-golf?
其实 我们好久没打过迷你高尔夫了
Actually, we haven't played mini-golf in a while.
但是 没错
But, uh… yeah.
差不多就这样
That about sums it up.
你去看谷仓 我去看主屋
You take the barn, I'll take the house.
我们帮助他人
We help people.
至少是努力帮助他人
At least, we try to.
就像卡西迪奥帮助我爸那样吗
Like, uh, Castiel helped my dad?
克莱尔 你爸爸的事
Claire, what happened to your dad…
我很抱歉 真心的
I'm sorry, okay? I really am.
但有件事你得知道
But, uh, there's something you gotta know.
你爸爸的牺牲并不是无谓的
Your dad's sacrifice was not meaningless.
他放弃了自己的身躯 他的皮囊
Yeah, he gave up his body, his… his vessel.
因为这样 小卡
And because he did that, Cass…
小卡得以去拯救世界
Cass was able to save the world.
世界啊
The world.
你父亲是个英雄
Your father's a hero.
他并没有枉死
He did not die in vain.
最后一个洞了
Last hole.
这么快啊
Already?
嗯 看这个
Yeah. See?
最后一球打完后
They take your ball on the last one.
就把球杆这样放进去
Drop it in the bottom like so.
你没事吧
You okay?
不是中风了吧
You're not stroking out, are you?
那个红印
The red marks.
什么红印
What red marks?
克莱尔 你真是个天才
Claire, you're a genius.
- 我们走吧 - 搞什么
- Come on, let's go. - What?
等等 我怎么天才了
Wait. Why am I a genius?
猎魔就这样吗
So this is hunting?
还要做功课
Homework?
小卡说罗尼像是被天使之刃刺死的
Cass said that Ronnie's wound looked like an angel blade,
但那道红印却和天使之刃不符
but the red marks didn't match up with an angel blade.
但如果是天使剑呢
But if it was an angel sword,
就能解释伤口的大小和那道红印了
that would explain the size of the wound and the red marks.
因为剑会有剑柄
Cause a sword would have a hilt on it,
剑柄会留下印记
which could cause the … the marks.
你就从一根球杆上得出了这些结论
You got all that from a putter?
这就是你说的吗
Is … is this what you mean?
古利格利
Grigori.
看守天使
The watcher angels.
那他们是好还是恶
So are they good or bad?
有一些传说里说他们会帮助人类
Well, some of the lore says that they, uh, they help people,
有一些则说他们猎杀人类
and some says that they prey on people.
所以还得继续查
So…keep digging.
艾米莉娅
Amelia.
吉米
Jimmy?!
Jimmy!
艾米莉娅
Amelia.
吉米
Jimmy!
艾米莉娅
Amelia.
- 我到处找你 - 没事了
- I looked everywhere for you! - It's okay.
- 我想找到你 - 别这样
- I tried to find you! - No.
你夺走了我丈夫
You took my husband!
没事了
It's okay.
（迪恩来电）
小卡也不接电话
Cass isn't answering his phone either.
我不明白 古利格利后来堕落了吗
I don't understand. Grigori angels went rogue?
开始以人类为食了吗 为什么
Started feeding on people? Why?
我不知道 也不在乎
Don't know, don't care.
我这就去霍洛韦那儿宰了那畜生
I'm heading over to Holloway's to end that son of a bitch.
我猜猜 我得留在这儿了 是吧
Yeah, let me guess. You want me to stay here?
生日快乐 但别打我
Happy birthday. Don't shoot me.
走吧
Let's go.
对不起
Sorry.
我一般可以治愈任何伤口的
I'm usually able to heal any wound. You…
我一直在做梦
I was dreaming.
这么长时间以来 我都在做梦
This whole time, I was dreaming…
梦到找到吉米
of finding Jimmy,
让我们一家团聚
of putting my family back together.
你不是他了
You're not him anymore.
我看得出
I can tell.
是啊
No.
那吉米呢
Where's Jimmy?
你丈夫已经身在天堂
Your husband is in heaven.
艾米莉娅 我发过誓要保护你们一家
Amelia, I promised to protect your family,
但我没做到
and I failed.
克莱尔活着就好 她是最重要的
Not if Claire's alive. She's all that matters.
她还活着
Claire is alive.
她已经长成一个坚强的大姑娘了
She's grown up to be a very strong-willed young woman.
这才是我的好女儿
Oh, that's my girl.
我不该离开她的
I just … I shouldn't have ever left her.
我以为如果找到吉米
I-I thought if I could find Jimmy,
就能让一切回归正轨
I would make everything right.
我就不该离开她的
But I should've never left her.
我不该的
I shouldn't … I shouldn't…
没事了
It's okay.
你就是霍洛韦了
You must be Holloway.
这五十年来 是的
For the last 50 years or so, yes.
之前我叫詹金斯
Before that, I was a Jenkins.
再之前 我叫米勒
And before that, a Miller.
我真名叫泰米尔
My real name is Tamiel.
我是古利格利
I'm a Grigori.
看守天使
A watcher angel.
天使怎么还猎食人类了
Since when do angels feed on humans?
从人类诞生之初
Since the dawn of man.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你们的灵魂
Your souls…
是天堂的碎片
are little slices of heaven.
如果得到小心呵护
that are, if properly kept,
就是世间美味
delicious meals.
一顿能吃好几年呢
that can last for years,
几十年都行
Decades even.
你不是天使
You're not an angel.
你是个恶魔
You're a monster.
我更愿意称自己为美食家
I prefer to think of myself as a gourmand.
我在人间创造了天堂
I make heaven a place on earth.
让我得以好好活着 也能躲开那些
Keeps me alive and hidden from the rest of the failures.
自称天使的废物
that call themselves angels.
他们是废物
Oh, they are failures?
你的生活就很好吗
Yeah, 'cause you're living so large in your own life.
我们曾有上百人呢
There were hundreds of us,
但如今
but now…
每个人的名字都刻在剑上
Each of our names inscribed on our swords.
我们这群精心打造 设计的生灵
A brotherhood of perfectly crafted, engineered beings.
却派去保护你们这群
sent to protect you pathetic,
底层的可怜虫
bottom-feeding disasters.
跟紧我
All right, let's stick together.
先查谷仓 然后进主屋
First the barn, then the house.
如果要射击 瞄准胸部
If you have to shoot, aim for the chest.
这杀不了天使 但能拖慢他
It won't drop an angel, but it'll slow him down.
明白了吗
Got it?
明白了
Yeah.
他们还…
Are they…
我也不知道
I don't know.
会找人帮他们的
We will get them help.
我这样多久了
How long have I been like this?
两年
Two years.
迪恩
Dean.
克莱尔
Claire?
对不起
I'm so sorry.
亲爱的 对不起
Baby, I'm so sorry.
对不起
I'm so sorry!
好了
Okay.
我们快去找萨姆吧
Let's go find Sam.
克莱尔
Claire.
听我说 待在这儿 好吗
Listen to me. Stay here, okay?
不要乱跑
Do not move.
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
谢谢你们
Thank you, both.
妈妈 妈妈
Hey, mom. Mommy.
小卡
Cass.
出什么事了
What the hell happened?
听我说 霍洛韦…
Listen, Holloway is a…
- 是古利格利 - 古利格利
- Grigori. - Grigori.
- 古利格利 - 对
- Grigori? - Yes.
不
No.
他们是最初来到人间的天使
They were some of the first angels on earth.
是一支精英团队 后来堕落了
It was an elite unit that went bad.
但他们已经灭绝了 被摧毁了
But they're … they're extinct. They were destroyed.
不 有一些活下来了
Well, no, some survived.
他们在猎捕人类
And they've been hunting humans,
在他们脑子中创造天堂
making them create heavens in their minds.
然后以他们为食
and feeding off them.
这鬼东西在哪
Where is this abomination?
我不知道 我到处都找了
I don't know. I looked everywhere.
他一定是走了
He must've left.
妈妈 清醒点
Mom. Come on.
妈妈 不要睡过去 好吗
Mom, you have to stay with me, okay?
来 站起来
Come on. Stand up.
妈妈 没事的
Mom, it's gonna be okay.
好了
Okay.
谢谢你 亲爱的
Thank you, sweetheart.
她已经没治了 你知道的吧
You know there's no fixing her, right?
你真以为
You really think.
子弹能伤着天使吗
that's gonna hurt an angel of the lord?
不
No!
妈妈 妈妈
Mom! Mom!
妈
Mom!
不要
No! Uhh!
妈 妈妈 千万别睡过去
Mom? Mommy, please stay with me, okay?
妈
Mom?
妈妈 妈妈
Mom. Mom. Mom.
妈妈
Mom.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
妈妈 对不起
Mom, I'm sorry.
艾米莉娅
Amelia.
吉米
Jimmy?
真的是你吗
Is it really you?
这里是…
Is this…
这里是天堂
It's heaven.
我…等了你好久 我…
I…waited for you for so long. I…
她怎样了
How was she?
克莱尔怎样了
How's Claire?
吉米
Oh, Jimmy,
她已经亭亭玉立了
she grew up so beautiful.
她好坚强
She's so strong.
就像她妈妈一样
Like her mom.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
那么 怎么着
So, what?
那是个收留迷途少女的中途之家吗
This is some sort of halfway house for wayward girls?
不 完全不是
No. Not at all.
乔迪·米尔斯是个好人
Jody Mills is good people,
她会给你个住的地方
and she'll give you a place to crash.
让你慢慢缓过来
until you get back on your feet.
不是永久性的
It's not forever, right?
你准备拿克莱尔怎么办
What are you gonna do about Claire?
这不取决于我
It's not up to me.
你说过死亡并不总是永别 对吧
You said sometimes death isn't always good-bye, right?
那么再见也未必是再也不见
So good-byes aren't always forever.
没错
Right.
好好照顾自己 克莱尔
Take care of yourself, Claire.
我很过意不去要把枪收回 所以…
I felt bad about taking the gun back, so…
（疯狂高尔夫）
谢啦
Thanks.
（天使传说）
但我可不想再做什么功课了
But I don't think I'm interested in any more homework.
你真以为我没看见你拿了这个吗
Do you honestly think I didn't see you take this?
你逗我呢
Really?
我就把书放这儿了
I'll just put this in here.
克莱尔…
You know, Claire…
你已经报了仇了
you already got your revenge.
你如果踏上我们走的路
You go down this path … our path…
活不长的
it's not a long life.
那可不一定 你看起来就挺老的
I don't know. You seem pretty old.
谢谢
Thanks.
听着…
Listen…
之前 我给你下套…
what I did, setting you up, um…
对不起
I'm sorry.
- 我不该… - 别放心上
- I just … I shouldn't … - Forget it.
都过去了
It's in the past.
你不会有事吧
Are you gonna be okay?
我吗
Me?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我会一直抗争下去的
But I will keep fighting.
我会一直战斗 直到一无所有
I'll keep swinging until I got nothing left.
你能照顾点他吗
Will you keep an eye on him?
他已经遭受了太多
He's been through enough.
你也是
So have you.
克莱尔 干蠢事之前千万做好功课
Claire, do your homework before you do anything stupid, okay?
如果需要我们 我们随叫随到
And we're here if you need us, any time.
我帮你把行李拎上车
I'll get you loaded up.
克莱尔
Um, Claire.
假如你有任何需要
If you, um, if you… need anything,
不管什么 我…
ever, I'm … I'm …
只希望你知道…
just wanted you to know that…
某人告诉我她会没事的
Someone just tell me she's gonna be okay.
是啊 小卡 当然
Yeah, Cass. Of course.
她会没事的
She'll be okay.
你也一样
So will you.
你这是回家还是离家
Going home or leaving home?
回家吧
Just…going.